Are you okay?
"KÔKÔ KYÔSHI"
VOL.1: "KINDAN NO AI,
FUTATABI"
Are you okay?
Your first time cutting class?
You shouldn't have made
such a scene!
Here.
Put these on.
Let's do this.
Got the camera?
Abracadabra!
Music by
SENJU AKIRA
Theme Song
"Bokutachi no shippai"
Koga Ikumi
FUJIKI NAOHITO
Machida Hina
UETO AYA
Kudô Beniko
SONIM
Kamiya Yûji
NARIMIYA HIROKI
Tajima Emi
MANABE KORI
Only one minute!
If you can solve it in one minute,
she's all yours.
What?
You don't want a stupid one,
right?
I know these.
There's a trick to them.
Ten, nine, eight, seven... sex!
Hey! Wait!
Why did you try to make
friends with me?
As soon as my suspension was
over you wanted to be friends.
You're such a prissy girl.
You really get on my nerves.
I'm going in there.
Don't come after me.
Presented by #Japan-TV
on Aniverse, ETG, and mIRCX
Support Japanese dramas
Buy region 2 DVDs!
Not for sale, rent,
or auction!
Timing
ARREST_HORN
Editing
KAMUI6
Typesetting
THESOG
Quality Check
Encoding
THESOG
Translator
YUJI
Hardsubs Transcribed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
Special Thanks to
KAMUI6
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Fujimura Tomoki
KYÔMOTO MASAKI
Tachibana Yuriko
MANO AZUSA
NOW TAKING BETS
Betting is about to end.
They're off to a good start...
Goal!
At that time I was just afraid
to be alone.
- We won!
- I wasn't searching for love.
Being alone scared me
so much.
You did it! That was fast.
You said your job was
in computers?
Quality control. Mainly for places
like dams and power plants.
You were laid off?
My father was too, recently.
Probably because
of the recession.
I quit though.
Not that it really matters.
And you?
Me? I'm... a stylist. I'm 20.
Excuse me.
Producer
ITÔ KAZUHIRO
Directed by
KAMOSHITA SHIN'ICHI
I think I went a little
overboard before.
- You at home?
- I'm at a restaurant.
You're not home yet?
Stupid!
Who's with you?
He solved the cube
in a few seconds.
What are you talking about?
- Hello?
- I'm okay.
What do you mean, okay?
Who does she think she is?
A Production of
TBS ENTERTAINMENT
Production Copyright
TBS
- Did you just move in?
- Yeah.
Come on in.
Thanks for inviting me in.
That's cool.
It's instead of using notebooks.
What's this for?
It's from Newton's Principia.
Book I, Proposition XX,
Problem XII.
It's about ellipses, parabolas,
and hyperbolas all being related.
What's that?
It's kind of gross looking.
It's Thomas Wright's depiction,
infinite universes
with God's eye at the center.
He tried to explain the phenomenon
of the Milky Way
through mathematics.
You obviously don't understand.
That's not necessarily true.
Really?
- Well...
- Of course.
How about a shower?
A shower?
Do you want to go first
or should I?
I...
I'll go first, then.
Go ahead.
- All right.
Hello?
You're not still with him,
are you?
Well...
I kind of went back to his
apartment with him.
His apartment?!
- Apparently he just moved in.
- Idiot!
You shouldn't go home with guys
you don't know.
At first, no-one knows
anyone.
He didn't drag you there did he?
Won't he let you go home?
Don't worry!
I'll be there soon.
What's so funny?
You're a nice person after all.
Aren't you worried at all?
Why am I getting all worked up
over this?
Just give him the phone.
I'll let him have it.
He's in the shower.
What are you thinking?
You're gonna get raped.
Get out of there.
- Did you know about me?
- What?
If I hadn't approached
you at school,
would you have known
who I was?
What are you talking about?
Even if you had seen me around,
you didn't know my name, right?
I'm not the type that
stands out.
What's your point?
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
You would have forgotten me
after we graduated.
And what's your point?
My grades are about average.
Same with sports...
My family is middle-class.
I don't understand. What does
this have to do with anything?
I'm a plain, boring girl.
You even said I get
on your nerves.
That was...
I don't think I'm ever going
to change.
- Goodnight.
- Wait a second!
See you at school.
Principia.
It's freezing!
The shower is broken.
You'll catch a cold.
I can't afford to catch a cold.
Sorry!
Um... I think... well...
You might be angry after we're
come this far, but...
You just broke up with
your boyfriend?
What?
Basically, you became a bit
desperate, but you can't forget
your ex-boyfriend or something.
Am I wrong?
- No. You're pretty close.
- I see.
I'm really sorry.
Not a problem.
Maybe I'm better off this way.
So you lost a loved one?
Or quit your job and then...
- ...I got desperate?
- Yeah.
Something like that.
I guess we're in the same boat.
We shouldn't be throwing
ourselves at each other.
That's right.
But somehow we ended up here.
Yeah. But sometimes things
turn out that way.
In life, you have to put up
with a lot stress.
- Going home?
- Yeah.
- I'll take you.
- I'll be fine.
Then I'll give you money
for the taxi.
I have money. Don't worry.
Okay, then.
This is kind of strange,
isn't it?
Yeah. I wonder why.
If you don't mind,
why not spend the night?
But...
Just to sleep.
I won't do anything.
You can tie my hands
together.
Can't you just sleep beside
me tonight?
It's my one wish in my
whole life.
Your whole life?
I'm going to die soon.
Not really.
I'll stay.
Haru no komorebi no
naka de
Kimi no yasashisa ni
- Good morning!
- Is that all you have to say?
Sorry for hanging up
on you last night.
I got worked up about it
and I couldn't sleep.
Sorry to have worried you.
I just don't want to be held
responsible if something
- happens to you.
- Like what?
Recently there have been some
horrible crimes going on.
You're more serious
than I thought.
- That's enough!
- Sorry.
Whatever. So...?
You went home after
I called, right?
You're not normal, Hina.
Really?
What's with the smile?
You're weird.
I always wanted someone
to tell me
that I'm weird, or different.
- Really?
- Yeah.
So you left in the morning?
Yeah.
What about your parents?
I told them that I was studying
at a best friend's house.
I've never been caught before,
so they didn't question me.
- Best friend?
- Yeah.
And you casually spent
the night with some guy.
He didn't seem like
a bad guy.
You can't tell by looking
at a person.
Yes, you can.
Not by their looks,
but just somehow I knew.
You were the same way.
- Me, too?
- Yeah.
People were spreading
rumors about you,
but I thought they
were wrong.
Exactly who was spreading
rumors?
I can probably guess anyway.
And?
Since you spent the night,
it's pretty obvious.
But I'll ask anyway...
You slept with him, right?
- That's a secret.
- What?
Not that I care.
What are they doing?
There's a new math teacher.
Remember, Shimamura-san
is off on maternity leave.
So?
Just like before, they're putting up
a math problem
that even university professors
can't solve.
That's bullying.
A classic Hamilton-Jacobi
equation.
First, K = C2.
S = integral.
Is he right?
- Let us begin.
- Stand.
Bow.
Sit.
What is it?
Do you have a question?
What are you doing?
I'm Koga. I'll be taking over
Grade 11 math
where Shimamura-sensei
left off.
- What page are we on?
- Page 106.
Everyone, open your books.
I'm head teacher of Grade 11,
Fujimura.
Nice to meet you.
Have you met the principal
and the head teacher?
Oh, I see. Good to hear.
The teachers will finish classes soon,
so I'll introduce you to them.
Oh, here is Tejima Emi-sensei.
She teaches the classics.
She just started last spring.
With her good looks, she seems
wasted on the teaching profession.
Wait. That could be counted
as sexual harassment.
Stop teasing me, boss!
My name is Tejima.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Koga. Nice to be working
with you.
Here is the Japanese history teacher,
Miyada Kôji-sensei.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the math teacher, Koga.
Are you single? You're quite young
to be working here.
It's quite rare for someone like you
to come along,
because this is a girls school.
You can smoke over there.
You smoke right?
Tejima-sensei doesn't like it though.
- Sir.
-Yes?
I'm still single, too!
Here is Muramatsu Tamotsu,
the gym teacher.
Your looks aren't a problem.
What's that supposed to mean?
How rude! Even you,
Tejima-sensei!
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize, but...
- I'm Koga. Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
I'll take you on a tour
of the campus, if you'd like.
With junior colleges, transition
to universities have become easier.
As a result, grades at this school
haven't been getting any better.
At best, we're the top
of the middle range.
But the girls seem to have a lot
of success with English.
- Why do you think that is?
- Why?
Because I'm the English teacher.
The sports teams are all
quite standard.
The tennis team that I managed
was able to get to the Tokyo
championship, though.
What sports are you good at?
Not your thing? But we have to put
you in charge of something.
Here's the language lab.
Since I became in charge,
we've upgraded the speakers.
As a result, the students'
listening skills have improved.
I heard from the director that you're
quite talented.
Huh? Not really.
You were in the Ministry
of Education.
Was there a problem?
Nothing in particular.
I'll tell you something.
The director likes people
with fancy resumes.
Just because someone is bright,
it doesn't mean they'll make
a good teacher.
The other teachers
are worthless.
I'm the only good
teacher here.
I'll warn you right now.
If you're here to look down on me,
we're going to have a problem.
Those aren't my intentions.
Excuse me. Maybe I've been a bit
stressed out recently.
No need to show you
the prep room.
You won't be going
in there anyway.
- Goodbye!
The amount of bathrooms
here is very small.
But be sure not to use the ladies
room, even if its empty.
You won't just get fired,
you'll be arrested.
You've got to be kidding.
The new teacher is the guy
you spent the night with?
This isn't a joke, right?
- Do you have any questions?
- Goodbye!
Not at present.
If you have anything on your mind,
just let me know.
Thanks.
One day I woke up and I was
a senior teacher.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
It must be a different person.
He didn't even respond.
- We're both in the same boat.
- You mean he doesn't know?
I was wearing make-up. I told him
that I was 20 and a stylist.
But don't you think he'd
recognized you?
Even though you had sex?
You were with him until
morning, right?
You didn't make this all up,
did you?
I didn't!
He's different from this
morning.
- You...
- Yes.
You're a student of mine?
Yeah.
But wait, you don't know
who I am?
I'm the new math teacher.
Yeah...
Today we had a class.
- Grade 11?
- Right.
Sorry. Which class were
you in?
- Class B.
- Oh.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THIS BUS WILL GO BY
JAPAN WOMEN'S MEDICAL
UNIVERSITY
Young residents these days!
You'll never learn to be surgeons!
What on Earth are you
here for?
How is teaching? Do you think
you can get used to it?
Who knows.
You're lucky that the director
is a patient of mine,
and I was able to get
you the job.
The director is always complaining
about some ailment.
You shouldn't be on your own.
- Don't you agree?
- I do.
At your old workplace, you were
surrounded by computers.
You didn't get a chance
to speak to anyone.
That's a bad environment
for you.
Yes.
How about your girlfriend?
ISHIKURA KAORI
That's her.
She never gives up.
She's obviously worried
that I suddenly quit my job.
- Did you tell her the truth?
- No.
It's for the best.
She always calls, but I never pick up.
So she keeps trying.
Why not just say you've fallen
in love with another woman?
Tell her she's a nuisance
and to stop calling.
She'll think you're a monster.
Does that bother you?
Sorry for talking like this.
Not at all.
But in the end,
you're doing her a favor.
It's better for her to be able
to forget me.
It's a standard way to end
a relationship.
And then she'll be able to find
a new boyfriend.
It sounds so harsh,
but this is real life.
I...
You're very brave.
Good boy...
- Come on!
- Get lost!
At least come
for a drink with us.
Guys who try to pick up chicks
like this are so lame.
If you're just hanging around like
this, you obviously want a guy.
I'm not joking.
- Hey, you just sighed, didn't you?
- What?
- Who the hell are you?
- Now, wait a second.
Hold up, guys. A girl can get
wrinkles just by sighing too much.
- Who do you think you are?
- Let's go.
It's their fault, right?
First lesson!
If you approach a girl three to one,
you're going to scare her.
Second lesson!
It's not a great strategy
to be too obvious.
Last but not least!
Because girls believe
in stuff like fate,
you have to play along.
You!
And another big sigh.
Just do what I'm doing
for a sec.
I'm your personal genie!
I like to stand out,
so I made a bit of scene.
Or did I help you out
for nothing?
No.
So why don't we go
for some karaoke?
Or would that bring me down
to the level of these guys?
Just as I thought.
Help me...
In Grade 11 we will cover all
of Japanese history.
We have been going
quite fast,
but from the third semester
we start the 20th century.
Let's talk about when
the Western date system
started in Japan.
It started in 1901 at Keiô University
when they had a party
to usher in the 20th century.
The head teacher asked you to help
with patrol tonight, right?
It's cold.
Did you bring a change
of clothing?
Our duties outside of class
are pretty difficult.
Also, don't forget about managing
a sports team.
It's not a big deal though.
Just organizing competitions
and stuff.
But... I...
The gym teacher,
Muramatsu-sensei.
Huh?
He's not that great looking,
but until you came
he was quite popular.
He says that recently that's
all disappeared.
He was grumbling about it
in the teachers' room.
Here.
Not sure where to put
your eyes?
It's okay.
I couldn't believe it either,
but the girls wanted you.
What?
Didn't you notice?
You're very popular.
Look! They're all
staring at you.
- I'm Aizawa from Grade 12.
- Grade 12?
I quit the club a while back,
but swim sometimes for exercise.
I heard a handsome teacher
became the new manager.
Do you have a girlfriend?
That's not a question for a student
to ask a teacher.
You can ask me, too, questions that
teachers aren't supposed to ask.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yeah. He's a university
student.
But recently we're just been
going though the motions.
For a romance to go on,
you really need some kind
of stimulation.
Oh?
You need obstacles to work
through together.
Like a relationship between
a teacher and a student.
Tejima-sensei,
you look great!
If I passed you on the street,
I wouldn't recognize you.
Let's go!
Put your phones down!
What grade you girls in?
Grade 12. Class A.
Hey! Stop!
What grade?
Are they our students?
They don't look like it.
There aren't too many
of ours tonight.
Thank you.
This isn't working.
Why don't we go grab
a beer somewhere?
We could make it Koga-sensei's
welcome party.
Can I ask a question?
Do you know about the student
that was expelled last summer?
Her name was
Suzumoto Taeko.
The one that worked
in the sex trade, right?
It's good we dealt with her
before her parents found out.
She was one of my first students.
A really good one, too.
You don't need to feel responsible.
We can't watch them 24/7.
That's right.
It's not your fault!
I talked to her.
She was lured into the business
by a host at a club called "J".
J?
There.
Newton...
Principia.
- SENDING MESSAGE
- MESSAGE SENT
It went through!
I know that girl.
Did you know she committed
suicide?
What?
Yeah.
You don't seem to feel
guilty about it.
I'm sorry!
Please forgive me!
I heard that she
was very rich.
That's all I told myself.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry...
I'm sorry! It's all my fault!
If he had gotten back up, I would
have given him a beating.
I really know how you feel about
your students now.
Maybe you should slow
down on the drinks.
Anyways, I'll be off now.
Cheers to Tejima-sensei's
love!
We can't be fooled
by that idiot.
- His name was Yûji, right?
- Sensei!
Just because he got down on his
knees, it doesn't mean he meant it.
While he was hunched over,
his back was laughing at us.
And you?
Do you plan to continue
teaching forever?
I really don't know.
Can I bum a smoke?
You smoke, too?
Don't you feel like you want to teach
at a university or something?
Not necessarily.
I see.
We've had a young teacher
like that in the past.
I was also young at one time.
He was a biology teacher,
I think.
When I look at you,
I'm reminded of him.
And that teacher went on
to a university?
No.
Maybe one day you'll hear
about him.
A STRANGE PERSON
IS FOLLOWING ME. I'M SCARED
Please take him home.
What shall we do?
Find another place to sit down?
I should probably
be getting back.
Why not just one more?
Well...
- I'm kind of tired.
- You are?
- And there are still trains running.
- It's too bad.
But have a safe trip home.
- Good night, then.
- Good night.
Good night.
We should both be heading
home, too.
- I'm still okay.
- But...
There's no problem.
We're both adults.
I'm sorry. Maybe I've had too
much to drink.
You!
I'm sorry.
I'm not your type anyway.
My type?
Unfortunately, there seem to be
no women that are my type.
Fujimura-sensei...
Taxi!
Wait!
Was Yûji really laughing?
I was so incredibly lonely.
Everything I did was in vain.
No one I talked to understood.
Would my exasperation slowly
turn to resignation?
I'M IN THE CONVENIENCE STORE
BY YOUR PLACE.
BY YOUR PLACE. I'M SCARED
- SENDING MESSAGE
- MESSAGE SENT
HELP ME
1) SEND
- SENDING MESSAGE
- MESSAGE SENT
MESSAGE RECEIVED
WHERE ARE YOU?
THE PARK
- SENDING MESSAGE
- MESSAGE SENT
I thought you were kidding.
You lied to me before, right?
That you were 20 and a stylist.
You recognized me?
Yeah.
Then why?
You're a student, so I figured
I couldn't say anything.
But you were kissing that girl
from the swimming team.
She kissed me.
If a pizza comes that you didn't
order, would you eat it?
- I see what you mean.
- Good!
I didn't think I'd ever
see you again,
so I let some of my weaknesses
show.
Weakness?
That I wanted you to stay
beside me all night.
Like a child who had
a bad dream?
Even though I'm an adult.
So you pretended you didn't
recognize me.
Right.
Not because I'm just some
simple, boring girl?
Huh? No.
That's good.
I...
I'll probably have a normal life,
get married, and have two kids.
Maybe that's supposed to be
happiness, but what if it isn't?
For some reason I just started
thinking that way.
I wanted a secret all
for myself.
A secret?
Even if I'm not happy
in that new life,
I would have a secret
from my past.
But why do you want that?
My father was laid off, and my
whole family was left suffering.
I just don't know.
I would like to go back to being
my normal self.
If only I had that secret
to take with me.
But if the only person that shares
that secret with me...
...doesn't remember it,
there's no point.
I'm happy that you
remembered.
Haru no komorebi no
naka de
Kimi no yasashisa ni
Umorete ita boku wa
Yowamushi dattan da
yo ne
At that time,
I wasn't thinking at all.
Not about the horrible
thing I did to you.
The game I played with you
that can't be blamed on my
love for you.
2019-08