"KÔKÔ KYÔSHI"
Haru no komorebi no
naka de
What about the life
expectancy?
Only five percent of patients
of this disease survive.
I'd say six months at most.
It's a warm color.
I'm not really dying, am I?
I'm only 17.
At that point I don't think
I understood the purpose
of my "experiment".
Why?
Because it wasn't true.
I was going to tell her.
To explain that it wasn't her who
was going to die - it was me.
Stand.
Bow. Sit.
This girl's fate isn't the same
as mine.
What lies in her future?
I don't love you anymore.
When I'm in love,
I wanted it to last forever.
I'm sorry. It's true.
You're going to...
Of course I don't go
to host clubs!
Don't misunderstand.
We're not trying to punish you.
I understand that a girl your
age wants to experience
different things.
You're being quite lenient.
That's right. Usually what you did
would be grounds for expulsion.
Thank Fujimura-sensei.
You're just scared
of my parents, right?
They contribute so much
to the school.
Money can't buy you
respectability.
If students stop coming to our
school, there is no more school.
We can't afford these kinds
of distractions.
Next time, we won't be
so understanding.
Are you threatening me?
Why not try and follow
the rules?
Sorry about that girl
in my class.
Corporal punishment doesn't have
a place in schools today.
Of course not.
But that doesn't mean
you can't discipline them.
If you aren't firm,
they'll walk all over you.
I'm sorry.
- Could I have some, too?
- Sure.
"If you aren't firm,
they'll walk all over you."
There used to be this teacher
I hated.
He was a gym teacher.
What a moron.
But...
Now I sound just like him.
Strange, huh?
Still, I'm sure she won't
go back.
Thanks.
Somehow I don't think that host
will give up so easily.
He knows that she's rich.
That's why he's after her.
You seem to be enjoying
yourself.
After a while,
just teaching gets boring.
You know?
VOL.3: "NEMURENAI
FUTARI"
Presented by #Japan-TV
on Aniverse, ETG, and Rizon
Support Japanese dramas
Buy region 2 DVDs!
Not for sale, rent,
or auction!
www.jtv-drama.org
Sorry to have kept
you waiting.
I understand you overheard
the discussion
I had with your teacher?
Is it true?
What did your teacher say?
- That it was.
- He's right.
I can imagine how you
must feel.
There isn't any sort of cure?
Unfortunately not.
What about a different
hospital?
If you want a second opinion,
I can write a letter
of recommendation.
Sorry, I don't mean to question
you're competence. But...
For the right price a doctor
somewhere can be convinced
to perform some kind
of procedure.
But that might just lead
to premature death.
I know it sounds harsh.
Oh, really?
Go ahead and sit down.
Why are you so worried anyway?
He...
Your teacher...
Your...
I see.
What should I do?
What should I do at a time
like this?
What am I saying?
Good question.
You just have to be strong.
Strong?
My homeroom teacher is really
easy, so it's no big deal.
But my grade supervisor...
When he's involved,
it can get scary.
Which teacher?
What's his name?
It's Fujimura.
Oh, Fujimura-sensei?
I just wanted to see what
a host club was really like.
But, I guess I'm not supposed
to go there anymore.
Oh? I'm hurt.
That isn't anything
against you.
I wouldn't mind meeting you
like this, or going out.
So you don't really care about
me one way or the other.
You probably have lots
of girls.
- Why, because I'm a host?
- Yeah.
- They're just customers.
- I can't see it like that.
I'm naturally very jealous.
You don't really look it.
If my boyfriend worked as a host
I'd be really worried.
It wouldn't work.
Really?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You guys again?
Looks like you two
are having fun.
You owe us for giving
her away.
You guys want
to get beaten up again?
Hey! Wait a second.
- What is this?
- Don't do this in front of her.
- Scared of getting caught?
- About what?
The other night was all a joke.
We were all in on it.
- You're not serious?
- Why don't you ask him?
I paid you guys, right?
You didn't pay us damages
for beating us up.
Yeah. I was in the hospital
for days.
Stop with the jokes.
Shut up and hand over
the cash.
This is all you got?
You must be a lousy host.
You!
I asked the wrong guys
for help.
You're right.
I hope you two live happily
ever after.
So you knew all about me?
- I knew that you were rich.
- I should have guessed.
That's what it was
at first, but...
You prick!
Wait, Beniko!
Listen to me for a second!
Or not...
How did we do?
This is where the fun
begins.
WELCOME HOME
Takeout food again?
Yeah.
- Does it surprise you?
- Huh?
That I'm acting normal.
- Yeah.
- I didn't go to school today.
- I know.
- I got up to the school gate.
- Yeah?
- But I just decided not to go.
Really?
And then I went
to the hospital.
- Oh. Now I get it.
- Huh?
So you heard the truth
from the doctor?
Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- What do you mean?
What do I mean?
About lying.
Part of me wished you had lied
and told me I was fine,
but I don't know.
Even hearing the doctor say it
somehow it just doesn't seem real.
- She told you?
- Yeah.
Apparently, I can't be saved.
But for some reason
it hasn't sunk in.
I mean, I feel fine.
I have a great appetite, too.
Well, the...
It's like being told by a fortune teller
that I'll be in a car accident.
Somewhere inside me, I believe
that it won't happen.
- Are you eating?
- What?
Yeah.
But it's the truth, I guess.
- What do you think?
- About what?
I mean, everyone dies
at some point.
True.
I guess it's scary because you
won't know what the world
is like after you die.
And I guess it's sad to think
that everyone
will eventually forget you.
That's stupid.
Eventually the people
who remember you will die, too.
Right?
I guess you could put it
that way.
I'm not scared at all.
Maybe I'm being too bold.
I'm surprised.
You're like other kids
these days.
These days?
Like those juvenile delinquents
who think that
because their lives are empty,
then so are everyone else's.
I wonder.
Maybe you're right.
Personally,
I can't understand it.
How can anyone say
they don't fear death?
To say you're not sad
that you'll be forgotten.
- I don't get it.
- Sensei?
I thought you'd be more
frightened.
You weren't at school, so I figured
you were crying alone at home.
You were worried about me?
I was relieved to see you
so normal.
Nobody knows about
your illness yet.
I guess I'm the only one you can
express your true feelings to.
- Well...
- Well, what?
It hasn't sunk in yet?
The doctor told you, right?
Dying isn't frightening
or sad?
Why are you upset?
I'm not. I just don't get it.
You don't understand?
You wouldn't know what it's like
to be in my position.
You're right.
If you're not going to eat,
go home.
I have to make the test
for tomorrow.
Can't I stay a bit longer?
I can't make the test
in front of you.
I guess you're right.
- Hina isn't here today.
- Okay.
What's your name? I might be
able to answer your question.
Oh, here he is. Please hold.
Boss, it's the phone.
Line four.
Hello, this is Fujimura
speaking.
Is it a woman?
No. It sounded like
a young man.
Oh.
Understood. Bye, then.
What does he want,
calling you up like that?
Sorry to drag you along.
I should really have brought along
Tejima, the homeroom teacher,
but she gets really
emotional.
And I have a poker face?
You seem like a reasonable
person.
Of course, you might just
be pretending.
Everyone pretends to be
something else,
whether they're good at it
or not.
Welcome!
Sorry. I fell asleep.
- And what do you want?
- No time for chitchat?
- Coffee, please.
- Sure thing.
Is this about Kudô Beniko?
She seems to have
blown me off.
She won't come to my
club anymore.
Of course she won't.
She's a minor.
She says she's scared of you
and that she'll be expelled.
- And?
- I guess I lost this time.
A sensible girl wouldn't
let you fool her.
No. It was just bad strategy
on my part.
Bad strategy?
Yeah. She's a naive girl
with tons of money.
She has lots of material things,
but emotionally she's empty.
So obviously she's looking
for a knight in shining armor.
That's what I read,
but I guess I was wrong.
This is what you came to tell us?
To admit defeat?
Defeat?
In a way.
All of this is just a game.
There are winners
and losers.
But, it's not over yet.
I think I'll try for a comeback.
Why not change your target?
I'm sure there are many others.
- I hate to lose, you see.
- So what now?
A declaration of war against
us teachers?
If the game is to continue,
it's only fair that I get help.
It's like Final Fantasy.
Let's just go. There's no point
listening to him.
Right.
I hate teachers.
At first I thought she came because
she was worried about you.
Her name is Machida
Hina-chan, right?
But she seems to think that
it is her tumor, not yours.
Yeah.
Obviously she misunderstood.
After all, she was taken
to the hospital
after hitting her head.
Right.
But you lied to her
when she asked you.
I was a bit agitated, and it accidentally
came out that way.
I figured that she'd discover
the truth after talking to you.
Yes.
So why didn't you tell her?
Why did you keep
my lie going?
I guess it's against my duty
as a doctor.
I'm your doctor. Not her's.
If my patient wants it that way,
I won't say anything.
When she talks with her parents,
she's sure to find out.
She was worried about
money.
If there was no chance of recovery,
she didn't want her parents to know.
That's what she said.
And I told her there was nothing
to be done.
Hearing that,
she just accepted it.
What a strong girl.
Very different from you.
Maybe it's the difference between
men and women.
It's just an act. I was the same
at first, too.
You try to convince yourself
that it's okay.
"It's no big deal. Everyone dies
at some point."
You just put up a strong
face to the world,
as though everything
was fine.
It's just an act.
- For her, too.
- Bye-bye, onêchan!
Bye-bye!
I'M BACK
Found you!
How long have you
been here?
I've been playing
with the kindergarten kids.
Cutting school to play again?
I'm a good student, so my
attendance is way above average.
Here.
My dad...
My dad has started
drinking a lot.
He must be worn out
from job hunting everyday.
Really?
My mom started working,
and now all they do is fight.
So...
You just don't want
to go home?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I couldn't sympathize
with you.
I guess I'm stressed
with this job.
You're not angry anymore?
But why were you shrugging
it off so easily yesterday?
You're not responsible
for me anyway.
That's what it's about?
If I just cried about it, you'd probably
get fed up with me.
Just like how my mom gets fed
up with my dad's complaints.
If you turn me away
then I'll have no one.
So you're happy to receive
sympathy?
I don't know. I'm not sure anyone
has really understood me.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
You poor thing.
There's no reason
for you to worry.
Get it? You're...
You're...
What are you two doing
in there?
Ouch!
GOOD MORNING
- Good morning.
- What?
What do you mean?
You're like a different person
from last night.
I'm not a morning person.
Yesterday you said,
"You poor thing."
- I did?
- Four times.
- I guess.
- Only you know about this.
So what?
If you want more sympathy,
why not tell everybody?
It's not necessarily about
sympathy.
Then what do you want
from me?
Only you know about this.
- So what?
- Huh?
I don't like you when you
get this way.
Well, I don't like you
when you act like this either.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
- "Good morning."
- There's a swimming meet today.
- Really?
We need you to time
the races.
I'm a bit busy.
- I'll help you out.
- Thanks.
- "Thanks."
- You really have to come.
- Okay, then.
- Later.
Sensei.
Good morning.
Is that guy someone's
boyfriend?
I wonder why he's here.
There's no question that he's
the same guy from the club.
- None.
- Tejima-sensei, don't worry.
I'll go bust him up.
He's not actually inside
the school grounds.
He just has his bike stopped
on a public road.
- But!
- Just as the boss says.
- Should we warn Kudô?
- Yeah.
- Were you two in a fight?
- I told him it was over.
- Why?
- He made everything up.
Made what up?
Apparently he knew that my
family was rich.
I wonder who he heard
it from?
He must have something
to tell you.
I bet he just wants to make up
more excuses.
Maybe he's after a different
girl now.
Like the daughter of the restaurant
owner in class C.
Maybe you're right.
That's not so bad.
Look! He's drinking milk
and eating bread as well.
More importantly,
are you okay now?
About what?
You had a cold, right?
Don't give it to me.
Kudô Beniko-san, please report
to the teachers' room immediately.
They're calling you!
It's all his fault.
Beni...
Nothing.
If you want the yogurt,
go ahead.
Okay, thanks.
I did knock.
Tejima-sensei told me
to come here.
She's your homeroom teacher
but I'm in charge of your well being.
I have no interest in him.
All right, then.
Just don't hang out with
him anymore.
I should just ignore him,
right?
Yeah.
You can go now.
Um... Sensei.
- Yeah?
- Why are you single?
In the past did you have a big
falling out with someone?
- And if I did?
- Oh, nothing.
Stop it! Stop it!
Please go now.
Okay.
Did I ask something bad?
Two minutes 18 seconds.
Two minutes 21 seconds.
Two minutes 17 seconds.
Does that girl want
to join the team?
No idea.
Ready!
- What?
- Huh?
Is there something
you want?
I just came to talk
to Koga-sensei.
I'm sorry, but he's helping
the team right now.
Oh.
He's been waiting all day.
So he wasn't waiting
for me.
Whatever.
Kids these days just don't have
any common sense.
It looks like that guy
finally left.
I wonder what it was.
- Tejima-sensei.
- Yes?
How would you like
to go out for a drink?
- For real?
- Are you paying?
Sorry, but just the two of us.
I'll be waiting outside.
It's not that I don't understand
the way you feel.
You're looking to depend
on somebody.
And I guess that person
is me in this case.
Am I depressing?
I'll try to act cheerful.
No matter how hard you try,
it's easy to see through.
You're still so hard on me.
But I guess you're a bit better
than this morning.
I just feel so useless.
I can't do anything for you.
I'm not asking for anything.
When I was sitting
in the tube at the park,
you started to say
something?
You said, "Get it? You are..."
I guess I did.
How does the sentence end?
What were you going to say?
Sensei?
I broke up with my
boyfriend.
Really?
It was so boring there was no
point in continuing.
But you said it would be hard
to break up with him
without a real reason.
I told him that I was in love
with someone else.
Excuse me,
but I was still talking...
You didn't say...
...that he's my new math
teacher.
Come on, now.
I said that we would get married
after I graduated.
We weren't finished
talking yet!
He cried.
That just put me off
even more.
- Poor guy.
- No! Poor me.
Dating a man like him.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I don't feel sorry
for you at all.
We can't do this! Stop it!
I'll see you tomorrow
at school.
Stop it! There's no point
in thinking about this.
Óscar Domínguez's
La pétrification du temps.
Think in three dimensions.
Think of two different seconds
of a single lion's life.
Basically between those seconds
you can break the lion's life
into infinitely smaller pieces.
Spherical geometry is analogous
to triangles larger than 180 degrees.
And in the case of it being smaller
than 180 degrees, the radius...
Poor me.
- Hello?
- Sensei?
Oh, it's you.
I'm sorry about today.
You've apologized
so many times.
I was hoping you didn't
catch a cold.
I'm fine. You're worried about
something like that?
It's strange.
I never thought I'd snap
like that.
Usually, I keep my anger
bottled up.
Yeah.
Maybe it's because
of my illness.
I don't like it. I'm becoming
a bad person.
Or maybe I was always
like this.
What time do you think it is?
Oh, I'm sorry.
But...
I can't sleep.
At that point I began to understand
the implications of what I was doing.
I remember trembling
all over.
Hey.
Tell me what you wanted to say,
that time at the park.
All right, sure.
I wonder why.
Huh?
At night you become
really gentle.
I like the voice
of the gentle you.
It makes me feel better.
It was like looking
at a mirror.
We were feeling all
the same things.
That time, I was going
to say this:
Yeah?
"Get it? You're..."
"You're not alone."
I'll always be there for you.
Written by
NOJIMA SHINJI
Music by
SENJU AKIRA
Theme Songs
"Bokutachi no shippai"
"Samishii kumo"
Koga Ikumi
FUJIKI NAOHITO
Machida Hina
UETO AYA
Kudô Beniko
SONIM
Kamiya Yûji
NARIMIYA HIROKI
Tejima Emi
MANABE KAORI
Muramatsu Tamotsu
ÔKURA KÔJI
Ezawa Mami
AOI YÛ
SUZUWARA DAIKICHI
YAZAWA KÔJI
TSUJI YOSHIHITO
AKASAKI RENA
NAGAO ASAMI
FUJII SAYURI
SORA EMIKO
HASEGAWA EMI
ABE ERINA
MAEZONO RISA
NITTA RYÔ
KANDA KANTARÔ
ICHIBA YÛSHIRÔ
GEIPURO
GEKIDAN HIMAWARI
GEKKIDAN IROHA
Fujimura Tomoki
KYÔMOTO MASAKI
Tachibana Yuriko
MANO AZUSA
Translator
YUJI
Editor
LEPERCOLONY
Timer
AREST HORN
Typesetter
THESOG
Karaoke/SFX
BUBU
Raw Provider
KAMUI6
QC
THESOG
Encoder
Hardsubs Transcribed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
Special Thanks to
KAMUI6 & AVALLAC'H
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Producer
ITÔ KAZUHIRO
Directed by
YOSHIDA KEN
A Production of
TBS ENTERTAINMENT
Production Copyright
TBS
2019-08