"KÔKÔ KYÔSHI"
The horoscope said that I should
go on a date this weekend.
Do you want to go with me?
- Our first date!
- If it rains, we should just cancel.
It worked!
Using Cantor's diagonal argument
you are able to see that
infinity reaches beyond
natural numbers.
Stop it!
Suicide just isn't the answer.
Didn't I say I was here for you?
That I'd always be by your side?
- Really?
- Really.
Darn! I almost had it too!
- I did it!
- What?
It's the first time you called me!
Why would you do something like that
to someone who's worried about you?
I always wanted to try,
but I decided not to.
You thought it'd be a nuisance?
No. At the park you said you'd be
thinking about me all the time.
- Did I really say that?
- You said you promised!
Fine then... so why the problem?
I'm always the one
who calls you.
- Oh, the phone bill?
- That's not it!
Well... I guess there's a bit of that.
Next time just call and hang up.
I'll call you back.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
What was I trying to say again?
You said it's always you that calls.
Sorry I waited to see if
you'd call, but...
I was happy.
I'm not about to kill myself.
I'm more positive than before.
- Stop yawning.
- Go on then.
I don't know how long I have to live,
but there's lots I have left to do.
Stuff you haven't done yet?
Like eating really nice food.
You could pay for it.
Me?
And going places I've never been.
Also...
Oh! I forgot my phone!
- At my place?
- I think so.
We'll have to go back.
Just go ahead! We shouldn't be
at the station together anyway.
You're right. Here's the key.
I'll put it in your shoe box
at school.
Also...
The thing I want to do most...
At that time, there were differences
between us.
Like that carefree positive
energy of hers.
I...
I want to fall in love.
I was always running
from the truth.
I said it!
- Excuse me!
- Welcome.
I made a double!
Presented by #Japan-TV
on Aniverse, ETG, and Rizon
Support Japanese dramas
Buy region 2 DVDs!
Not for sale, rent,
or auction!
www.jtv-drama.org
...and she escaped with the young
man on the bike.
There's no room for argument.
As Kudô Beniko's homeroom
teacher, I feel responsible.
There's nothing you could
have done.
Those things are left up
to Fujimura-sensei.
Expulsion is the only answer.
We must maintain the integrity
of the school.
What about the contributions?
The contributions her parents
make every year?
Are you sure this is the place
for that sort of talk?
Why not let me solve this problem?
But...
We won't bother the principal
about it just yet.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
The principal won't know,
and the money is important
to the school.
- Yes, but...
- Something else?
With the girl last year,
you didn't do anything.
The same host has come back
for seconds at our school.
- Don't you find that strange?
- Yes, of course.
If they were girls
from good families,
they wouldn't be tricked so easily.
- Can't you see where he's going.
- Where?
He might have an insider
at the school.
He couldn't...
I doubt it too.
It's just a precaution.
If we don't stop this here,
it will just continue next year.
It's not that I'm giving Kudô
special treatment.
Understood. Excuse me.
You really think there could be...
...an insider? Not really.
I selected "continue".
The game.
VOL.5 "MAYONAKA NO TAIKETSU"
Stupid! Don't follow me.
- Ouch!
- Hina.
The jewels?
I can get good money for them
at the pawnshop.
You took them without asking.
The money was earned by burying
dead people.
- Why say that?
- It's true.
But I'm surprised.
Even I'm surprised.
He told me he's never been
number one at anything.
Not school, not sports.
He looked so sad.
I understand him because
I'm the same.
Me too.
For girls its okay, but guys have
to go out into society.
Without confidence,
it's really hard, right?
I don't know.
But if I make him the top
seller at his club,
I know he'll quit for me.
I don't know about that.
When I left it was out of pure adrenaline.
I saw him standing out in the rain.
I knew I'd get expelled, but I had
this amazing feeling.
You're not expelled.
The council decided you were
just suspended for now.
- You're joking?
- The head of the grade saved you.
Fujimura-sensei?
Really?
So you still have a chance
to go back.
If you say you were tricked.
If you say he's a horrible person.
- I'm going.
- Wait, Beni!
The more people condemn him
the more I love him.
I can make this work.
You... why?
Why do you keep being
so kind to me?
Kind? I thought that I was being
quite severe.
It's for my own good.
Do you remember
the group counseling?
Yes.
Other patients were able
to express themselves.
- They'd relate to each other.
- Yes.
You were different.
You barely spoke.
That's right.
I thought you were definitely
headed for suicide.
And then shortly after...
It's because I'm weak.
Yes. That's right.
I've told you about my husband
before, right?
He passed away of cancer, right?
He was also a weak person.
Very much.
- What is it?
- Nothing really.
I doubt it.
Why? What are you doing here?
Nothing really.
He's not there.
- You're late!
- So sorry!
- Sensei!
- A teacher?
Yeah. Right now I'm teaching math
at a girls school.
- My uncle a teacher?
- Your uncle?
She's a student of mine.
Oh! I thought she was
your whore.
Shut up!
He's my nephew,
my big brother's son.
Nephew?
I'm Koga Shôta.
Nice to meet you.
- I'm Machida Hina.
- And what's she here for?
- What do you think of her?
- What do you mean?
Is she your type?
And how about you?
I get it.
What does he think he's doing?
Copying me?
And he walked you home?
Hello?
We parted at the station.
I told him to take you home.
- C'mon!
- What?
Is this because of what
I said this morning?
That's right. You said you wanted
to fall in love.
I did but...
You said that you were being
very positive.
But I figured you'll always
be down at times.
At times like that you don't want
to get desperate and go for anyone.
He's my nephew and if you
had him you wouldn't
- be desperate like that.
- I want real love.
Not you setting me up
with some guy.
Oh, I see.
He wasn't your type?
That's not the issue.
He plays rugby
and his marks are enough to get
into the top universities.
He's a pretty decent looking
guy too, right?
He gets lots of chocolate
on Valentine's Day apparently.
So why me, then?
Oh, I get it.
What?
You're more concerned
about yourself.
- Don't say that...
- I think he was into you.
And why is that?
He asked you for your e-mail
address, right?
So what?
Don't be modest.
You're a charming girl.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Your type?
I think so. I'll ask him.
- Not him.
- What?
- You?
- Me?
You took me home before
to sleep with me.
That was different. And you said
you were 20 and a stylist.
Strange guys will try
to pick you up.
And you're a strange guy.
Don't worry about me.
I said l'd always look after you,
but I can't always be there.
So... I'm sorry I wasn't very
delicate introducing you.
- But I'm thinking of you when...
- Idiot!
Hello?
Huh?
This is an automated answering
machine.
What's her problem?
- Good morning!
- Oh! Good morning!
- Um...
- Yes?
Is there like a male equivalent
to PMS?
Like wanting to be with someone
one day and alone the next?
I wonder. In my case...
You talk to Fujimura-sensei
a lot, right?
Well not that much.
- Could you...
- Yes?
Does my name ever come up?
Not really...
Fujimura-sensei kissed me.
What do you think?
I don't really know.
Would you ask him
for the truth?
Me?
- Class is starting!
- Okay!
When a and c aren't 1...
log ab = log ca / log cb.
The reason is that P =...
P = log ab.
Hello.
Hi.
Do you ever get dizzy?
Do you get tired easily?
Are these symptoms
of my illness?
- Headaches?
- Not yet.
Are you able to sleep?
It depends. Not last night.
They must be symptoms.
At your age, even little things
will make an impact.
- But...
- How is your appetite?
Strangely it's...
- Good to hear.
- Yes.
Poor you.
Just now you sounded a lot
like my teacher.
Koga-kun?
He said that to me before.
In a gentle way like that.
Really?
It makes me feel better.
Is he kind to you?
Sometimes he is and sometimes
he isn't.
- Sometimes he isn't?
- He's just a bit moody.
That's horrible, considering he
knows about your illness.
I guess.
And it makes you uneasy.
I am uneasy at times.
I feel like when he's kind to me
I feel fine
and when he's cold with me
I feel uneasy.
Depending on somebody
is natural.
- Depending?
- Right.
You feel like he's the only one
who understands you?
Is dependence different from love?
I think about him all the time,
but...
...it's different. It's an illusion.
Thinking like that will just
make you sad.
- Sad?
- Don't you think?
Even if you think that way
about him,
how does he think about you?
He's a teacher and you're a student.
And he's much older.
Basically, he's nice to you because
of your illness.
Even if he's sympathetic,
that isn't love.
Think about how he feels.
I understand how you feel.
It must be hard.
But if you really want to fall in love...
...you must do it with somebody that
doesn't know about your illness.
My feelings for him are an illusion.
Yes.
And it's just a feeling and not love.
I must be a real idiot.
I'm sorry to talk to you this way.
It's okay.
Anyway, I'll give you some medicine.
Okay.
Koga-san!
Koga Shôta-san?
Hey!
I went overboard in sports today.
Wow! Your room is so empty.
- Told you so!
- All you have is a TV!
I don't like hanging around
at home.
Even so...
Answer the phone. One of your
customers, right?
Nah. Don't worry.
I'm not going to get bothered
by something like that.
I know what your job is.
Sorry. Just give me a second.
Yes?
- Tonight's on schedule.
- What was it again?
I told you about that person
I wanted you to meet.
Oh! The math teacher, right?
Do you really think it'll work?
Trust me. I was right about
the other girl, right?
You got me there.
I have a gift for noticing people
with borderline personalities.
- See you later.
- Sure.
What are you guys doing here?
- Yûji!
- Get over here!
He owes us money!
You're his girlfriend, right?
You pay us back...
...with your body!
Yûji! Yûji!
- Stop it! Please!
- Shut up!
What did you throw away?
Dependence.
Nothing.
What should we do after eating?
Did my teacher tell you
to do this?
- What?
- To look after me or something?
Are you a princess or something?
Yes, I am.
Tejima-sensei said that?
She said she wants to know
the truth.
- I'm sorry.
- No problem.
There are two opposite things
I tend to look for in women.
On the one hand I like wholesome,
well-spirited women.
On the other hand understanding
each other is important.
Not even that, it's emotion
that's important.
Someone who shares my abnormal
level of emotional depth.
The wholesome person would be
Tejima-sensei, right?
But when I try for a woman like that,
I feel my spirit drying up.
The second type of girl isn't
Kudô Beniko, is it?
It's sad how easily she can fall into
the lap of somebody like that.
And you don't want to save her
because you're a teacher, but...
I'm not sure if it's that I want
to save her or just be with her
when she's down like this.
Sorry for bringing you along.
Just tell Tejima-sensei what
you have to.
- I'm not sure if I can.
- I'm counting on you.
I'll be heading out then.
- I'll kill them!
- Stop!
Your debt is cleared, right?
Beniko.
I'm fine.
I'm so sorry!
It's so close! C'mon!
You can do it!
- You did it!
- Here.
- Thanks! Look at it!
- Stop it.
- What are you doing?
- Excuse me, I forgot my key...
- Good evening.
- You?
Here we are.
Right on. Let's start the game.
Die!
Hey!
Sensei?
You're still here? Run! Quickly!
Stop it!
No need to worry.
What are you doing here so late?
Forgot something?
Your key, perhaps?
- What is this about?
- Don't be angry.
I told you I wanted us
to get together.
I want you to be my friend.
So you were the insider?
I'm good at spotting weak people.
What do you mean?
Relax! I'm going to show
you paradise.
I want paradise too!
Life shouldn't be boring.
We're fed up with what society
has dealt us.
We don't want to be the horse
pulling the cart.
We want to be the ones sitting
on top, enjoying the view.
It's easy to take control.
Forget about morals. Just put
doubt behind you and go for it.
Do what you want without
any worries.
Think of it like a game.
Sorry, but I don't want
to be like that.
No way!
You said yourself you don't believe
in all that eternity crap.
That's not the same.
I took the janitor out from behind
with this bat.
He didn't see our faces
and we're all wearing gloves.
If you hold this bat, you become
the prime suspect.
They'll think you did it because you
were new and the pressure built up.
How foolish.
Great. Now you're with us.
If you don't cooperate we'll leave
you here till morning.
I'll call in to the cops anonymously.
Don't try anything.
We're too strong.
Please, Sensei. Just give up
and come over to us.
Let's have fun. You never know
when you're going to die, right?
You try too! It feels great.
Think of the window as this
despicable society.
Break everything!
- Do it!
Way to go!
Keep it coming!
If you're gonna break one,
might as well break more!
- Here's half.
- Thanks.
Damn! I missed.
I missed again!
We won!
Not again!
What?
Hey!
Sorry. I'm going home.
It's not everyday I can play chess
with a math teacher.
So let's make it worth something.
If you win, I'll let you go.
- Yûji.
- Shut up. The winner gets a prize.
It's so cold.
- Everything is girl's stuff.
- It's a girls school after all.
Oh! I found some gym clothes.
- Take a whiff of those, man!
- Stop it, perverts!
Stop it! Just take it home.
They should really mind
their manners.
Hold me close and hold me fast.
The magic spell you cast.
This is la vie en rose.
When you kiss me, heaven sighs.
And though I close my eyes.
Maybe he's asleep.
It worked!
Obviously.
Sensei?
You guys go home.
Do what you're told.
Tetsuya, keep watch out front.
Sure thing.
Good luck, Sensei!
Hey! Don't you want him
to become one of us?
True. Okay, bye.
You used to work
for the government, right?
An elite engineer.
Mathematicians and physicists
always impressed me.
Nobel invented TNT. Oppenheimer
invented the atomic bomb.
Geniuses are really good
at destroying the world.
Looking for this?
- Please!
- When we finish the game.
It's a toy.
I know a lot about medicine.
You could say I'm a distributor.
I suppose it's natural not to believe
in the afterlife.
You won't be around much longer.
Checkmate.
Congratulations.
That night, for one instant,
I felt tempted to go over
to his side.
I knew the thing that was stopping
me from doing so...
...was the girl who represented
the hope in my life.
Haru no komorebi no
naka de
Kimi no yasashisa ni
I thought to myself that
perhaps one day,
one day she would come
and save me.
Written by
NOJIMA SHINJI
Music by
SENJU AKIRA
Theme Song
"Bokutachi no shippai"
Koga Ikumi
NFUJIKI NAOHITO
Machida Hina
UETO AYA
Kudô Beniko
SONIM
Kamiya Yûji
NARIMIYA HIROKI
Tejima Emi
MANABE KAORI
Muramatsu Tamotsu
ÔKURA KÔJI
Ezawa Mami
AOI YÛ
Koga Shôta
SAITÔ SHÔTA
SUZUWARA DAIKICHI
YAZAWA KÔJI
SHINJI TSUICHIRO
AKASAKI RENA
NAGAO ASAMI
FUJII SAYURI
SORA EMIKO
HASEGAWA EMI
ABE ERINA
MAEZONO RISA
NITTA RYÔ
KANDA KENTARÔ
ICHIBA YÛSHIRÔ
SAITÔ TAKEO
GEIPURO
GEKIDAN HIMAWARI
GEKKIDAN IROHA
Fujimura Tomoki
KYÔMOTO MASAKI
Tachibana Yuriko
MANO AZUSA
Translator
YUJI
Editor
KENSHIN`MACLEOUD
Timer
AREST HORN
Typesetter
THESOG
Karaoke/SFX
BUBU
Raw Provider
KAMUI6
QC
THESOG
Encoder
Hardsubs Transcribed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
Special Thanks to
KAMUI6 & AVALLAC'H
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Producer
ITÔ KAZUHIRO
Directed by
IMAI NATSUKI
A Production of
TBS ENTERTAINMENT
Production Copyright
TBS
2022-08