HYÛGA JOSHI SENIOR
HIGH SCHOOL
"KÔKÔ KYÔSHI"
- Here!
- Thanks.
We'll come back
for the container.
You're a lucky man.
The students don't care as long
as you're young and single.
- Aren't you young and single?
- Oh, that's right!
Don't feel like you have
to eat it all.
It's a women's trap. If you get fat
they won't give you a second look.
- Tejima-sensei?
- Yes.
Take a look at this.
Thank you.
This is really good.
- What is it?
- Oh...
Nothing.
I messed it up.
I wanted a secret all
for myself.
But if the only person that shares
that secret with me...
...doesn't remember it,
there's no point.
I'm happy that you
remembered.
He helped me get away
from that pervert.
I get it!
And you wanted to thank
him for that.
Wait!
I think I'm having my period!
If you don't mind,
why not spend the night?
Just to sleep.
Can't you just sleep beside
me tonight?
It's my one wish
in my whole life.
I'm going to die soon.
I got hungry watching
you eat.
- Here.
- Really?
- I made a lot.
- All right, then.
You didn't put any poison
in this, did you?
At that point I was torturing
myself inside.
- Prank call?
- No.
It's my girlfriend.
Are you in love?
The more important something
was, the worse I acted.
It was like a big joke.
Hello, darling!
Sure, let's meet up.
Where is good?
That's right.
They're meeting at that
café "Peach".
Presented by #Japan-TV
on Aniverse, ETG, and mIRCX
Support Japanese dramas
Buy region 2 DVDs!
Not for sale, rent,
or auction!
www.jtv-drama.org
VOL.2: "SENSEI NO
HIMITSU"
Solve this if I call
your number.
Five minutes should do.
Doesn't this kinda suck?
Numbers 14, 15, 16 come
to the front.
Damn! I'm number 16.
To be honest, the students
don't like your class.
Understood.
All you do is write problems
and make the students solve them.
Trying to cut corners,
are you?
Obviously you're just trying to gauge
the level of the students, right?
Math is about repetition
and speed.
So you're doing
it on purpose?
Unlike memorization,
math and geometry require
actual talent.
For kids without that talent,
numbers will just put them to sleep.
We're not here to train
rocket scientists.
That's right.
It's not like I have any Olympic
athletes to teach.
We're here to allow students
to advance to university.
The most important thing is to make
sure no girls fall through the cracks.
- But that's so...
- Boring?
In that case,
maybe you should quit.
Excuse me.
Hey, who do you think
you are?
- I'm really sorry.
- Koga-sensei?
Hey there.
Don't you have class?
I have a review block and I saw you
coming here from the window.
Are you training with
the team today?
- I'm busy.
- To bad.
I was thinking of going too.
Why?
What do you mean?
Are you really asking?
Weren't you mad at me?
Because you pushed me away
after I kissed you?
I'm shy like that.
Maybe I came back to you precisely
because I was mad.
Sounds complicated.
It's simple. My boyfriend and I have
no spark right now, and no...
Why not break up, then?
If only I could find a new
boyfriend, then yes.
He'd ask why we were breaking up
and I wouldn't have an answer.
Just tell him there's
somebody else.
And there's no reply
for that.
How cruel.
It's worse to pretend to be nice.
You toy with people's
emotions that way.
Already looking
for the next victim?
Isn't this cute?
- That's so adorable!
- I'll take this!
Hey, wait!
When are you gonna be done
over there?
Today's history class will
be long, so let's...
What were you laughing
at back there?
- Huh?
- In the classroom.
- Nothing really.
- Okay, I'm done.
That's so gross,
you two holding hands.
What is it?
You said we were
best friends?
Yeah.
Oh... I'm sorry.
- Jealous?
- Shut up!
Beniko!
Hey, Kudô!
Where are you going?
- Where did she go?
- HYÛGA JOSHI
Now she's ignoring me?
- Yes?
- Hello? It's me.
- PEACH
- Welcome.
She's beautiful.
Welcome.
Go ahead.
- A café au lait.
- Understood.
- So it was true.
- What?
- That you became a teacher.
- Yeah.
- Do you know how to teach?
- Apparently not.
- That's not good.
- I guess.
Why?
About quitting my job?
You said you enjoyed the quiet
setting of your job.
And you talked about not having
to bother with lots of people.
I said that.
You vanished from work
for a month.
What were you doing?
I was confused.
I'm back on my feet now.
I'm not criticizing you, but why
couldn't you have talked to me?
I figured you'd object.
My wages are a lot lower
after all.
That's what it was?
And that...
...that was the reason you stopped
talking to me?
Well...
I was very worried.
Don't you understand that?
Worried?
Of course! You left your apartment
and your office empty.
And you wouldn't answer
my phone calls.
I did today, right?
How many times do you
think I called?
Exactly 100.
- I waited 'till the 100th time.
- Stop joking around.
Tell me what happened.
What is there to say?
There's something different
about you.
Maybe I'm a clone.
Be serious.
We even talked of marriage.
We met each other's parents.
Tell me the truth.
- The truth?
- What is it?
Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
Who's this?
At times like this,
men can never talk straight.
I'm sure he's just trying
to be nice.
- Times like this?
- Yes.
But to leave it at that doesn't help.
You need to know the truth.
About you two?
It's not that I don't like
you anymore.
Stop it with that.
I'm very sorry.
I didn't mean to...
There's nothing
to apologize for.
I'll pay.
Your wages are lower now,
right?
- It's okay.
- Thanks, then.
I want to show you something.
They only have it here.
All right, then.
This escalator goes up.
What is it?
He's my teacher. I don't think
he noticed though.
What? Is love forbidden
at your school?
I ditched school today.
I know that girl.
Did you know she committed
suicide?
I'm sorry!
JAPAN WOMEN'S MEDICAL
Couldn't you have dumped her
over the phone?
I didn't want to do it like that.
You actually made a student
pretend to be your girlfriend?
I figured it would go down
better that way.
She probably knows
it's not true.
But the girl's acting was great.
I wonder...
Women have good intuition.
It's odd that she gave up so easily.
Maybe it was a matter of pride.
You obviously just wanted
to meet her.
To meet her one last time -
or will it be the last time?
I bet you thought about telling
the truth, too.
You wanted to cry, confess
and be comforted.
That's not true.
You wanted her to look through
your silly charade
- and ask what's really wrong.
- You're wrong!
If you picked up after she called
enough, you'll probably confess
- if she asks enough.
- So what should I do?
I'm sorry.
It's okay to be honest
with me.
But only with me.
Okay.
Have a seat.
Good morning,
Koga-sensei!
Here, "Ashibiki no yamadori no
o no shidari o no".
It's known as naganagashi.
It represents a lonely bird
sleeping on its own.
Does everybody
understand?
- Okay, moving on...
- Wait!
What are you timing?
Nothing really.
Just makes me look busy.
Any word from your
girlfriend?
Thanks to your amazing
acting, none.
- Are you thankful?
- Yeah.
You do remember our agreement,
don't you?
You want to break up with your
boyfriend and it's my turn
to play the new love interest.
Right.
Sorry, but it's not gonna
happen.
What?
Is a teacher allowed
to break promises?
Now I'm a teacher?
- You seem to be fitting in.
- Not really.
I heard from the head
teacher.
You're resigning?
KUDÔ
It's huge.
I got it!
Stop it, Pooh-san!
Pooh-san?
Hi!
He's looks like a bear,
like Winnie-the-Pooh, right? So...
- Pooh-san?
- Yeah.
You're house is really big!
I'm surprised.
- Isn't it gross?
- No.
I was bullied when
I was younger.
Really? You seem more
like the type...
To bully someone?
Ah... yeah.
My family is in the funeral
business.
Funerals?
Kids said I was happy when
people died and called me
a zombie and stuff.
So I took a lot of time off school
and ended up a year behind.
You're different
from the rumors.
I have a habit
of victimizing myself.
I always take things that people
say the wrong way.
I feel like my friends aren't really
my friends.
I think maybe my teachers
or parents are just asking them
to hang out with me.
Stuff like that.
It happened for real once.
My parents paid some kid
to hang out with me.
I threw that person's flowers
back in their face.
I'm not saying that you're
like that.
I... get it.
And, I'm really jealous
of others.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry!
I'm just a little bit different.
My love is strong.
Saying it myself is kind
of funny.
I'm your friend.
I really like you a lot.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Let's always be best
friends.
What's wrong?
Don't worry.
You, too, Pooh-san.
We're very much alike.
Pooh-san.
I thought I told you to come
to me about anything.
If you don't talk to me,
we can't work this out.
I'm sorry.
If it has to do with your health,
that's one thing.
But leaving so soon is bad
for the students, too.
That's my official comment,
anyway.
You were an elite
civil servant.
I know that my comments about
your class must have offended you.
That's not it.
That's not the problem?
No.
It's just that I don't think
I was meant to be a teacher.
You don't have the determination
to do it?
Right.
Who does have the determination
these days?
Everyone just wants to appease
everyone else.
Everyone is trying not
to offend anyone.
It used to be different.
Students aren't looking for those
determined teachers anymore.
- What about you?
- Huh?
I mean,
what about you, sir?
I'm probably less cut out to be
a teacher than you.
- I don't really think so.
- You don't?
I'm wearing a mask,
you see.
A mask?
A steel mask.
I don't remember what I really
look like anymore.
Lost to resignation
and idleness.
- Welcome back.
- Thanks.
- Hi there.
- Kanpai!
Isn't this place expensive?
It's only 3000 yen for your
first time.
Maybe that's too much
for you two?
Sorry! I don't drink.
A little won't hurt.
Let's make a toast.
Come on, Hina, just one.
- Okay, then.
- Sorry! Just wait a second.
Where did you meet
this guy?
I was a bit shocked to hear
he was a host.
Don't worry.
He's not ripping me off.
I don't have that
kind of cash.
Tired?
You can go home early
if you want.
Grade 11, class B,
Kudô Beniko.
Do you know her?
No.
It's possible that she's being targeted
by the host from the other day.
Remember what happened
to the last girl.
What passion you have.
I'm not interested
in the students.
It's the host with those glassy
eyes that scared me.
Glassy eyes?
- He has no heart.
- By credit card?
Thanks for today.
It was fun.
Look at this!
Hina, watch out! Run!
Stop!
Wait!
- Get the students.
- Understood.
My favorite teacher.
Thanks for always.
Hurry up, Hina!
This way!
What the hell.
You've been drinking?
I feel sick.
Here.
If I go home like this,
I'll get in trouble.
- I am your teacher, though.
- Huh?
Oh, nothing. Open it.
You found my address through
the school?
Should you really be bringing
students home?
Guilty as charged.
The girl from before
was a student, too?
No, she was...
I could tell how old she was.
You made it all up.
I thought a lot after that.
There was no way you'd do
something like that.
- You overestimate me.
- No, I don't.
That's why I thought
of marrying you.
I don't pick people
who make me worry.
You always liked stability.
It's not just that.
I understand you very well.
You're delicate and kind.
I respect you for that.
And I'm thankful for that.
So I knew that it wasn't true.
What do you want me
to say?
Tell me the truth.
About why I changed
my job?
Forget about that.
I trust your decision.
What is it, then?
Tell me why you're trying
to leave me.
That was also my decision.
Don't you have
an explanation?
It's really abstract.
Basically, a lot of little things
put together.
I realized that our values
are different.
Did I try to force my values
upon you?
Neither of us did.
We just put up with each other.
And that added up?
I got bored of doing things
like having to socialize
with your parents.
I'm not good at that kind
of stuff.
- And so...
- I guess I wanted to escape.
Escape to a world where
nobody knew me.
And I chased you.
I don't give up easily.
No comment.
I did it because I love you.
- Love?
- Of course.
I love you.
And...
Love means understanding.
You didn't understand me.
You couldn't have loved me.
I'm sure I was the right kind
of man to marry.
But that alone doesn't make
a relationship.
Why are you being
so horrible?
Tell me! Why?
I can't believe that you'd say
such a thing to me.
I don't love you anymore.
I don't love you.
Oh.
Goodbye.
Farkas was a Romanian teacher
of mathematics.
He was dedicated to proving
the fifth postulate.
At the same time his son
was thinking of non-Euclidean
geometry principles.
In a letter he wrote to his son
about how futile it was.
He told his son,
"Trust me and give up."
Love is the same.
Your health, your peace of mind
and your happiness
go out the window.
Would you just go home?
Go!
Excuse me.
I think... that he is still...
Well...
It's just a hunch.
Thanks.
No problem.
Goodbye.
- Really? You got caught?
- I'm sorry.
It's no big deal. We won't get
expelled or anything.
Don't tell anyone, but my parents
make a big financial contribution
to the school.
Really?
This world revolves
around money.
- Money?
- So don't worry about it.
Hey, you two over there!
- Start moving!
- Sorry!
I love you.
- I don't love you anymore.
- Hina!
Are you okay?
Machida, talk to me!
Did you hit your head?
Get up slowly.
I'm okay.
In the end I lost them
in the crowd.
Anyway, it might not have
been them.
Are you saying that I saw
things wrong?
- Oh... no.
- I'll let it go this time.
I'm not trying to protect
the students.
There is one condition.
I didn't hand in your letter
of resignation.
Give it another chance.
- Wait.
- Yes?
Why?
Why am I stopping you
from leaving?
- Yeah.
- Because I'm your boss.
Stand. Bow.
- Sit.
- Open page 136.
Hina?
- Are you okay?
- What's wrong?
She hit her head earlier
in gym class.
Sensei. I'm okay now.
Lets just make sure.
Maybe I'll get really smart,
like you.
- I'm stupid.
- Why is that?
Because you broke up with such
a beautiful woman?
I bet you were in love
at first.
Yeah.
But that feeling just started
to go away?
It's scary that either yourself or your
partner could end up like that.
And you?
I haven't had that kind
of experience yet.
I haven't loved or hated.
I see.
But when I'm in love,
I wanted it to last forever.
Never changing.
But I'm sure you wanted that
for yourself as well.
Who knows.
Of course you did. Nobody tries
to hate somebody on purpose.
We did a CT scan to be safe,
but the doctor said
there was no problem.
- Thank you.
- How are you?
Would you like to rest
for a bit longer?
- I'm ready to go.
- Wait a minute.
I'll go tell Fujimura-sensei.
Excuse me.
Is Koga-sensei here?
- The person you were with?
- Yes.
I think he's in the examination
room.
Do you ever have
double vision?
Yeah.
It's also called polyopia,
and it's taking effect.
It's due to the growth
of the brain tumor.
What kind of symptoms
should I expect?
Well...
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look this way!
- I won!
- Darn, I lost.
- Daddy, l won! Bye-bye!
- Bye-bye!
Brainstem glioma is a horrible
kind of tumor.
The brainstem is the most
important part of the brain.
The brainstem controls
consciousness and breathing.
You should already be experiencing
polyopia and moderate loss
of motor control.
The disease will continue
to worsen.
Eventually you won't be able
to move how you want
and breathing will become
difficult.
- What about the life expectancy?
- What?
Only five percent of patients
of this disease survive.
Even with surgery, there is only
a small chance of success.
How long?
It's horrible, but it afflicts
young people the most.
I'd say six months at most.
Really?
You.
It looks like she heard
about you.
So this is where you were.
Isn't it nice?
Did you know that it takes eight
minutes for the sun's light
to travel to earth?
In other words, this light
is eight minutes old.
It's a warm color.
Yeah.
The warm light that's eight
minutes old.
It's not true, right?
I'm not really dying, am I?
I'm only 17.
What? You?
I'll be dead in six months?
At that point I had lost my research
and my girlfriend.
I was in despair and ready
to give up.
Why did I think that was
an excuse, though?
It's not true, right?
Sensei...
I'm sorry.
You could say it gave me
the hope to live.
It could have been anyone.
Anybody else.
Someone to perfectly understand
all my pain and frustration.
It's true.
You're going to...
Ashita ni nareba
dono yô ni
Written by
NOJIMA SHINJI
Music by
SENJU AKIRA
Theme Songs
"Bokutachi no shippai"
"Kimi to samishii kaze ni naru"
Koga Ikumi
FUJIKI NAOHITO
Machida Hina
UETO AYA
Kudô Beniko
SONIM
Kamiya Yûji
NARIMIYA HIROKI
Tejima Emi
MANABE KAORI
Muramatsu Tamotsu
ÔKURA KÔJI
Ezawa Mami
AOI YÛ
SUZUWARA DAIKICHI
YAZAWA KÔJI
TERADA CHINATSU
AKASAKI RENA
NAGAO ASAMI
FUJII SAYURI
SORA EMIKO
HASEGAWA EMI
ABE ERINA
MAEZONO RISA
Ishukura Kaori
KOJIMA HIJIRI
GEIPURO
GEKIDAN HIMAWARI
GEKKIDAN IROHA
Fujimura Tomoki
KYÔMOTO MASAKI
Tachibana Yuriko
MANO AZUSA
Translator
YUJI
Editor
KENSHIN`MACLEOUD
Timer
AREST HORN
Typesetter
THESOG
Karaoke/SFX
BUBU
Raw Provider
KAMUI6
QC
THESOG
Encoder
Hardsubs Transcribed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
Special Thanks to
KAMUI6 & AVALLAC'H
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Producer
ITÔ KAZUHIRO
Directed by
YOSHIDA KEN
A Production of
TBS ENTERTAINMENT
Production Copyright
TBS
2019-08