"KÔKÔ KYÔSHI"
Good morning.
You poor thing.
It's done!
Great.
Get it?
You're...
You're not alone.
I'll always be there for you.
Red's my lucky color!
What's your sign?
Pisces.
Uh-oh. You'll have bad
luck today.
You're probably right.
Tired?
Yeah. I was on the phone with
a certain someone all night.
A certain someone?
When we finished it was an hour
too early to leave for school.
Why not sleep during class?
That's what I do.
A teacher sleeping in class?
Oh, maybe I should give a test.
That would be horrible!
I'm just joking.
Here.
- That's good.
- Yeah.
- Not about the test.
- What?
You're always so nice
in the evening,
but in the morning you're different.
You were great on the phone,
but I wondered what you'd be
like this morning.
- You came to test your theory?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna have some.
The TV horoscope said that I should
go on a date this weekend.
To an amusement park
or something.
It's not good to stay inside.
You should go for it.
- There's no one to go with.
- Just find someone to take.
It's a girls school.
I'm going to die soon, right?
- Want to go?
- Huh?
Do you want to go with me?
Can you go out with your teacher?
- I guess not.
- No! Let's go!
My guilt was becoming heavier
and heavier.
I could refuse Hina nothing.
What is it?
Our first date!
It's not a date! It's more like
babysitting.
Date! Date! Date!
- No it's not!
- Date!
As long as it was
a reasonable wish.
Presented by #Japan-TV
on Aniverse, ETG, and Rizon
Support Japanese dramas
Buy region 2 DVDs!
Not for sale, rent,
or auction!
www.jtv-drama.org
VOL.4: "KANASHII DÊTO"
What is he trying to accomplish?
He's working up the students.
It's hard to get them
to concentrate.
What do you think?
Fujimura-sensei.
We have no choice but to call
the police.
An amusement park?
Yeah.
Is that such a good idea with
a teacher? Before long...
Then again, you already had sex with
him before he was a teacher.
No, I didn't.
But you were with him
until morning.
- Nothing happened though.
- Whatever.
It's amazing though, isn't it?
That teacher is very popular.
- Really?
- Like you didn't know.
I can't believe you got him.
Like I said, I didn't "get him".
I guess you're kinda cute.
If you look real close.
No, I'm not. I'm plain.
You're the one who has your boyfriend
waiting outside the gates everyday.
I didn't tell him to.
He's really cool.
He's just after money.
Well, the teacher's just
pitying me.
How?
- Do you really want to know?
- Whatever.
- Then I won't say.
- I won't ask.
Feel free to use the textbook
while solving this problem.
Hina!
No way!
- Poor guy!
- Wait!
Hey!
Everybody, go back
to your seats.
This isn't a joke! Get off me!
Come on! Let go!
Let go!
- You're hurting me!
- Then get in the car!
How many times is she gonna
come in here?
She really bugs me.
What's she looking at?
Why the hell was she here before?
I don't get it. She's always
in the way.
What's she here for?
She's a nuisance.
You still haven't told her?
- No.
- Why not?
I was scared at night.
Because...?
The darkness takes hold of me.
The more I try to resist,
the more I get sucked in.
Even the sound of the clock
gets distant,
and I feel like I'm not in control
anymore.
It feels like I'm wasting away.
Sometimes I have to keep fighting
the fear and loneliness until morning.
You've said this many times.
Hina called me up, telling me
she couldn't sleep.
- So what?
- It made me think.
Maybe she was going through
the same thing.
You're using her like a mirror.
Right. Just like a mirror.
And I tried to make her feel better
by telling her she's not alone.
As I said that I...
You felt better yourself.
Right.
Isn't that a bit selfish?
I'm not trying to criticize you.
It's almost predictable for someone
with an illness like yours.
Of course I feel guilty.
I'm not going to say
anything bad.
Just tell her the truth right away.
It's not just for her.
It's for you, too.
I understand what you're saying.
It looks like she's going through
everything that you are.
But of course she isn't.
Just give me some more time.
She's not dying.
Surprise!
Of course she'll get angry,
but she'll start smiling
again quickly.
You aren't going to have
a happy ending.
After this it'll be even harder.
Who cares about the other thing!
Anyway, you have no idea what
I'm going through!
Koga.
Excuse me.
If you can't bring yourself
to tell her, I will.
That's not...
I could just say anything.
Like it's really a friend of yours
that's sick.
Shall I tell her?
Is it okay?
Fine.
I'll get you some medicine.
I'm okay.
I'll be going now.
Why don't you wait outside
of her house?
That sounds like something
a stalker would do.
- It's hard to draw the line.
- Gotcha.
Thanks to you, the cops gave
me a good beating.
Is this all part of your strategy?
Maybe so.
Did you...
Did you have a bad upbringing?
Abusive childhood?
Perhaps you're bitter towards
your mother,
and now you take it out
on women?
I'm sorry, but those excuses
are obsolete.
It's not like that anymore.
Why then?
I guess I have no reason.
Does that annoy you?
Come on, keep trying
to stop me.
I told you I enjoyed your
determination.
I'll leave you with a hint.
Teachers can't beat me
and neither can policemen.
You're all bound by the law.
Hamilton wanted to throw the old way
of doing things out the window.
Using a base of four,
he could calculate
that z = a + ib.
Hello?
Sorry for calling so late.
Can't sleep again?
Yeah. Maybe because I slept
in class today.
You were sound asleep.
About the weekend, it looks
like it's gonna rain.
Really?
If it rains, should we catch
a movie or something?
I'm looking at the movie times
for Shibuya and...
Hello? Are you there?
We should just call it off.
- Huh?
- If it rains, we should just cancel.
That's not fair. Why?
After all, I'm a teacher
and you're a student.
We shouldn't be seen together.
We could disguise ourselves
with sunglasses and stuff!
Sorry.
Hey, wait. It's dark right now.
Usually you're nice at night.
Hey!
What?
Sorry! There's construction in front
of my house, so the signal is bad.
You didn't hang-up
by any chance?
Well...
How childish!
No. The phone cut out.
Really?
Really.
- Really really?
- Really really.
You're making these things?
How many are you going to do?
Tons! Until the rain stops.
You make some, too.
Why should I?
If it's raining your boyfriend
won't be outside.
Who cares. I'm relieved
he's not out there.
Then why do you keep looking
out the window?
I'm not looking.
What do you girls want?
What are you doing?
Reading over my teaching
material.
- Here?
- Yeah.
You don't like other people,
do you?
- Depends on the person.
- How about rain?
Rain?
Good question.
- It depends on the kind of rain.
- What are you doing tomorrow?
- Tomorrow?
How about going on a date
with me?
Oh. So you've broken up with your
boyfriend and have free time.
Right. It's horrible being alone
on the weekend.
I think I'll pass.
Because you're a teacher
and I'm a student?
- I already have plans.
- No way, you're just...
I have plans with another student.
It depends on the weather, but we're
going to an amusement park.
- An amusement park?
- Yep.
- It's that girl, right?
- Which girl?
That grade eleven girl always hanging
around you. Even in here.
Yes, her.
That girl? Do you feel sorry for her
or something?
Maybe she feels sorry for me.
Don't come to the pool if you're
not on our team.
- What's this? How childish.
- Hey, that's the first one I made!
- Stop it already!
- Who are you to say that?
I heard from a friend you were
bullied in junior high.
- Stop it! I like that one.
- Are you an idiot?
Stop coming! You're bugging
the teacher.
- I'm bugging him?
- He says you're driving him insane.
- He said that?
- What?
- Of course he did.
No way.
If it rains, we should just cancel.
What are you doing? Class started
a long time ago.
Don't ever come back! Idiot!
Are you okay, Hina?
Hina!
What do you think you're doing?
No!
Fujimura-sensei?
I'm sorry.
About what?
I'm just not used to that
kind of thing.
- What?
- I should be sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
What?
Are you free tonight? I...
I made a mistake. I want you
to forgive me.
Hey. I'm free tonight...
- It's just an act.
- Even with the police?
Yes. He's just trying
to win you over.
But look at the rain. He'll die.
Don't think like that.
Could you do it?
Would you go that far for me?
Of course not. Not even my
parents would.
Wait.
I can't just ignore something like this.
It's not in my nature.
He's just doing it to get to you.
I want someone to care
for me like that.
I want him to see the true me.
- You'll be expelled.
- I know.
It won't lead to a good life.
What is a good life anyway?
Do you feel like you have
a good life?
He's heartless. It's all
a game to him.
- I'll change him.
- You can't.
How do you know?
Wait!
Stop her! Stop her!
Sensei.
You you think you can
sleep now?
Yeah.
I've thought about it
and I'm not going to tell
the truth to that girl.
Maybe I was a bit jealous of her.
Jealous?
In psychiatric terms,
"countertransference".
While looking after you,
my patient,
I began to feel attracted to you.
Attracted to me? No way.
Those kind of things happen.
Although, it's not real love.
So I was trying to get her out
of the picture quickly.
But it's not like I can come over
here every night.
Sensei.
If you need her, I won't
tell her the truth.
I'll try to keep my perspective.
I'll tell her the truth.
Sure, she has helped me.
But on the other hand, she just
makes me feel worse.
It's like you said. She can't
take my place.
She's not going to die.
I'll tell her. After that she'll probably go
back to being just another student.
So make me a promise.
Don't abandon me!
You're the only person who
really understands me!
Don't be so nice to me.
Sensei!
Get some rest.
If you don't sleep then
I can't go home.
I'd be too worried.
Thanks.
If you want coffee, I'll make it.
I know how.
Are you French or something?
Sleeping in the nude like that.
Oh...
It's good for your health.
Then you should lock the door.
I must have forgot.
What?
My hair. I cut it.
- Go get in the shower.
- Why?
Why do you think? Look!
- Look!
- What?
See?
With a sixty percent
chance of rain!
It worked!
Let's take a picture!
Come on! Just one!
Cheese!
This is freaky!
- You take the next one.
- Okay, here goes!
- Go!
- Cheese!
Sensei!
- You?
- What a surprise!
It sure is.
Which one should I get.
- This one please.
- Three hundred yen please.
This is Kazama Kiyotaka-kun.
He's a 3rd year university student.
Nice to meet you.
This is my math teacher,
Koga-sensei.
- Your teacher?
- Yeah.
What are you laughing at?
Hi there!
We just happened to run
into each other.
Is that what you're saying now?
You never know who's watching
in a place like this.
Koga-sensei decided to make
it a group thing.
- No, I didn't.
- He didn't know what to do.
Really?
Who knows.
If you don't spell it out for her,
she'll get confused.
Or is she a love interest
of yours?
- Of course not.
- See.
It's cute to give him notes
at school and stuff,
but don't try barging into his
private life.
I don't...
You don't what?
I don't have any feelings
for him!
I don't like him at all!
How childish to run off like that.
Doesn't that tire you?
- Maybe.
- Let's go!
- This way!
- Hey, stop!
Welcome, this way please.
Here you are.
- What are you thinking?
- Why?
- And what about him?
- What?
Leaving your boyfriend out
there like that.
He's not exactly my boyfriend.
I have lots of male friends
like that.
- I feel sorry for him.
- It's more fun that way.
He'll try even harder after
he sees this.
I get it.
- It's funny, right?
- Funny?
The game is more fun when there
is lots of trouble along the way.
- Game?
- Yeah. A game.
It's like Final Fantasy.
You sound like someone else
I know.
- Who's that?
- No one.
If you don't have fun,
it's your loss.
Everyone dies at some point.
If you don't have fun everyday
you'll regret it.
That's called hedonism.
It's stupid to spend all your
time worrying, isn't it?
- You're right.
- I knew it.
I never thought you were the type
who bothered with morals.
You seem more like someone
who's looking for a good time.
Am I wrong?
Or do you actually believe
in the afterlife?
No. I don't.
I don't believe.
So let's have fun together.
- Together?
- I'll take you along.
- Where?
- To a world with no worries.
- Sensei?
- I'm okay.
The ride is just making
me feel sick.
Sensei?
Thank you for coming
to the park today.
We will soon be closing.
Thank you for coming today.
She wouldn't...
I'm going to die soon, right?
She's not dying.
What are you doing?
It's dangerous. Please come down.
Someone help!
Stop it!
You can't do it.
I understand what you're feeling,
but you can't!
Think of the people you'll
leave behind.
Maybe it's impossible
to understand.
But suicide just isn't the answer.
People don't decide when
they are born.
Death should work the same.
That's the way life is.
You should live every day
to the fullest.
I understand that it's scary.
I understand the fear that you deal
with every night.
Didn't I say I was here for you?
That I'd always be by your side?
I'm sorry. Those weren't just words.
I promised you.
I'll be thinking about you morning,
day, and night.
I won't take my eyes off you.
Really?
Really. So...
Darn! I almost had it, too!
I bet it hurts.
What did you come back for?
I already won the game.
She's out of school, right?
It's over. Now get lost!
She ordered the most expensive
kind of champagne.
I acted like this...
"I've never been the most
successful host."
She's fell for it, and with all
the money she spends I'll be on top!
And then she asked me if
I would be satisfied
and willing to take
a respectable job.
- How heroic of her.
- He's just doing it to get to you.
I want someone to care
for me like that.
I want him to see the true me.
Bye now!
My girl is waiting.
It won't lead to a good life.
What is a good life anyway?
Do you feel like you have
a good life?
I choose "continue".
The game's not over yet.
I'll kill you.
Yûji! Long time no see!
Hi! I'll be over soon.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's make a toast!
Do you feel like you have
a good life?
No, I don't.
I'll take you to the station.
I'm fine. I told my parents I was
staying at a friend's.
You shouldn't say that.
I feel like I can sleep
so easily here.
I'll wake you for the last train.
In the end I wasn't able
to tell her the truth.
With her relying on me,
I was able to feel better
about myself.
At that point I made a vow.
I would look after her every
minute of every day.
That way she wouldn't
end up like me.
Haru no komorebi no
naka de
Kimi no yasashisa ni
Umoreteita boku wa
Written by
NOJIMA SHINJI
Music by
SENJU AKIRA
Theme Songs
"Bokutachi no shippai"
"Samishii kumo"
Koga Ikumi
FUJIKI NAOHITO
Machida Hina
UETO AYA
Kudô Beniko
SONIM
Kamiya Yûji
NARIMIYA HIROKI
Tejima Emi
MANABE KAORI
Muramatsu Tamotsu
ÔKURA KÔJI
Ezawa Mami
AOI YÛ
SUZUWARA DAIKICHI
YAZAWA KÔJI
AKASAKI RENA
NAGAO ASAMI
FUJII SAYURI
SORA EMIKO
HASEGAWA EMI
ABE ERINA
MAEZONO RISA
ARISA
SAITÔ NATSUKO
YASHIKIDA AYAKA
KASUYA SATOKO
TAKAHASHI MITSURU
FUJIWARA AKIRA
GEIPURO
GEKIDAN HIMAWARI
GEKKIDAN IROHA
Fujimura Tomoki
KYÔMOTO MASAKI
Tachibana Yuriko
MANO AZUSA
Translator
YUJI
Editor
LEPERCOLONY
Timer
AREST HORN
Typesetter
THESOG
Karaoke/SFX
BUBU
Raw Provider
KAMUI6
QC
THESOG
Encoder
Hardsubs Transcribed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
Special Thanks to
KAMUI6 & AVALLAC'H
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Producer
ITÔ KAZUHIRO
Directed by
IMAI NATSUKI
A Production of
TBS ENTERTAINMENT
Production Copyright
TBS
2022-01